[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is the dik-dik, indigenous to Africa?", "correct_answer": "Antelope", "incorrect_answers": ["Cricket", "Wild cat", "Rodent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did electrical engineering professor, Dr. Brent Townshend, invent in 1996?", "correct_answer": "The 56K modem", "incorrect_answers": ["Potato Chips", "Bookshelf speakers", "The remote control locator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the other name of the creature, which is often called the Abominable Snowman and is thought to inhabit the Himalayas?", "correct_answer": "Yeti", "incorrect_answers": ["Rodan", "Bigfoot", "Scylla"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest city in Switzerland?", "correct_answer": "Zurich", "incorrect_answers": ["Geneva", "Bern", "Munich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the CB radio handle of  Cletus Snow, the character portrayed by Jerry Reid in the movie Smokey and the Bandit?", "correct_answer": "Snowman", "incorrect_answers": ["Leadfoot", "Cruisin Cletus", "Big Daddy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Arnold Schwarzenegger initially rejected the offer to star in the 2003 movie Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines?", "correct_answer": "Because James Cameron would not direct the movie", "incorrect_answers": ["Because he didnt like the script", "Because he was planning to run for a Governor of California", "Because he had injured his back in an accident"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This phobia forces people indoors.", "correct_answer": "Heliophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Phagophobia", "Necrophobia", "Erythrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2005 film was directed by Tobe Hooper and features Star Treks Denise Crosby.", "correct_answer": "Mortuary", "incorrect_answers": ["The Rage", "Slither", "Hysterical"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous singer encouraged his fans to come to his concerts dressed in the purple colour?", "correct_answer": "Prince", "incorrect_answers": ["Hilary Duff", "Stephen Tyler", "Pink"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is represented by the chemical formula C12 H22 O11?", "correct_answer": "sugar", "incorrect_answers": ["salt", "oxygen", "baking soda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This food, made by bees from the nectar of flowers, gives great energy to the body. This energy is used mainly for blood formation.", "correct_answer": "Honey", "incorrect_answers": ["Sugar cane", "Beeswax", "Royal jelly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It Came from Beneath the Sea was a movie about a giant octopus that attacks New York.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]